OLUWADAMILARE IYANUOLUWA

FRONT END DEVELOPER AND UI/UX DESIGNER





Profile

Hello! I'm Iyanu, a front-end developer with experience in building user interfaces for web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript. I have a good understanding of responsive design and i'm proficient in front-end frameworks such as Bootstrap and React JS.

Contact 0 0 +234 906 039 4427 iyanuxn@gmail.com

Link

https://github.com/iyanuxn

Education

Bachelor Degree Computer Science University of Ibadan 2020 - Current

Skills

- Front end development
- Python development
- UI/UX designing
- Digital design
- Logo design
- Image manipulation
- Management and organization
- Collaborative engagement
- Proficient in communication

Technologies

- HTML, CSS, JS
- React JS
- Bootstrap V5
- Tailwind CSS
- Framer motion

Work Experience

Feb 2019 - Feb 2019 Ireland (remote)

Web developer

I leveraged a Content Management System (CMS) platform to meticulously design and develop a website tailored to the unique needs of a prominent church located in Ireland.

April 2021 - May 2021 Nigeria

Web developer

Employing Wix a CMS platform, I designed and developed a website to cater to the specific needs and values of an esteemed elderly care home.

May 2023 - May 2023 U.S.A (remote)

Front end developer

I crafted a React.js and Tailwind CSS landing page for a sneaker development monitoring platform.

Aug 2023 - Aug 2023 U.S.A (remote)

Front end developer

I had the privilege of serving as a Front-End Developer with Rogue Finance, a pioneering Web3 staking platform enabling decentralized staking on the MAV protocol.

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023 Nigeria

Front end developer intern

I was fortunate to intern as a Front-End Developer at the Training, Research, and Development Unit of ITeMS, a prominent division within the esteemed University of Ibadan.

Interests











Visual storytelling Drawing Digital design Photoshop SKateboarding

Socials



@iyanusama

